Rayyan Siddiqui

Address: 25 Franklin Crescent CR4 1ND

Mitcham, London

Telephone: 07473802889

Email: rayyansiddiqui2002@outlook.com

PERSONAL PROFILE

After achieving a high grade in BTEC Computing, I discovered a passion for the Technology sector hence why mainly Computer related subjects were chosen at A Level. In my spare time, I volunteer at charity events run by Human Appeal to aid those that are unfortunate and in need. I tend to work efficiently independently as well as able to work effectively with a team. Volunteering at charity events also allowed me to understand the work environment and also demonstrated to me how to handle work under pressure. Volunteering also presented how I can take leadership to handle members of my team as well as display a building of work relationships with maturity. Working with this charity has allowed me to collaborate and work in a team as well as experience challenges I would never have seen myself doing. Moreover, volunteering has taught me how to communicate with others as well as know how to react in tense situations. In addition to volunteering, I have gained a substantial amount of skills from my work experience program. Working in retail has taught me how to become approachable as well as helpful whilst staying on task. As well as this, I have also learnt how to collaborate and communicate with colleagues to ensure tasks are completed to my best ability.

SKILLS

- Team work
- Team player
- Communication
- Creative
- Charity event volunteer
- Able to approach and communicate with customers
- Proactive

EXPERIENCE

Human Appeal, Marylebone, London NW1 6XU - Borough Leader/Volunteer

October 2018 - Present

- Working with a team of volunteers aged 16-35 to run & organise events in order to raise money for charity
- Leaflet distribution and sales handling of event tickets
- As of now, my recently appointed volunteer role of Borough Leader requires for me to recruit volunteers aged 16-35 in the surrounding area in order to build a team to handle events and fundraise
- Attended retreats which have allowed me to work with a new team and also complete team building exercises
- · Handled donation money and counting money to gain an estimate of money raised

Robert Dyas, Wandsworth High St, London SW18 4TF - Work Experience

June 2019 - July 2019

- Working with a team of staff members to check & stock products
- Obtaining products from the stock room for customers
- Shadowing staff members at till in order to gain insight

Robert Dyas, Wandsworth High St, London SW18 4TF - Sales Assistant

September 2019 - December 2019

- Working with a team of staff members to check & stock products
- Obtaining products from the stock room for customers
- Serving customers at the till
- Restocking shelves around the store
- Following planograms for new product arrangement
- Completing Click & Collect orders for customers
- Observing & signing off money made in a day's work
- Being able to multitask whilst serving on the till
- Communicating with customers to ensure the best customer service

EDUCATION

Chestnut Grove Academy, Balham - GCSE/BTEC Level 2 and A

Level/BTEC National Level 3

September 2016 - August 2020

BTEC Level 2 - Computing - Distinction* Distinction* (A*A*)

GCSE 9-1 - English Language, English Literature, Maths & Combined Science - Grade 5

GCSE - Geography and DT - **2 C Grades**

BTEC Level 3 - Single & Double Computer Science - Distinction*Distinction*

A Level - Design & Technology - Grade B

References available

Jon Taylor (Head of Sixth Form, Chestnut Grove) - <u>jtaylor130.212@lgflmail.org</u>

Ebrahem Ettoubi (Fundraising Officer, Human Appeal) - <u>ebrahem.ettoubi@humanappeal.org.uk</u>

Daniel Tinkorang (Computer Science Teacher, Chestnut Grove) - <u>dtinkorang1.212@lgflmail.org</u>

Ramone Sutherland (Assistant Manager, Robert Dyas) - <u>ramone_sutherland@hotmail.co.uk</u>